Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation Records UA042
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Surveys and reports, 1900 -- 2007; 1965 -- 1999; UA042.001; 56.4 Linear Feet; 139 Digital Object(s)
  - ESL, 1995 -- 2005; UA042.001.029.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Factbook - Data warehouse, 2006 -- 2007; UA042.001.029.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Factbook faculty data summaries [1 of 2], 1992 -- 2003; UA042.001.029.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Factbook faculty data summaries [2 of 2], 1992 -- 2003; UA042.001.029.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Factbook historical, 2000 -- 2006; UA042.001.029.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Full-time and part-time student enrollment, 1995 -- 2006; UA042.001.029.00024; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Full-time students by program, sex and ethnic group, 1995 -- 2005; UA042.001.029.00025; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Geographic dist. of students by state / territory, 1995 -- 2005; UA042.001.029.00026; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - GSAS exit survey, 1999 -- 2003; UA042.001.029.00027; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
    - GSAS Exit Survey, 2003; UA042.001.029.00027.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Grad seniors by major, 1990 -- 2005; UA042.001.029.00028; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - International faculty / scholars, 1995 -- 2005; UA042.001.029.00029; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - International students, 1995 -- 2005; UA042.001.029.00030; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Lilly endowment, 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.029.00031; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Manos Project, 1996; UA042.001.029.00032; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Manos, Steve (Review IR), 2000; UA042.001.029.00033; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Masters degrees granted, 2006; UA042.001.029.00034; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - National indicators, 1987 -- 1988; UA042.001.029.00035; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - NEAIR paper 2000 [1 of 2], 2000 -- 2004; UA042.001.029.00036; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
    - NEAIR Tables, 2004; UA042.001.029.00036.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Paid Personnel - Total by campus, 2005; UA042.001.030.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Paid Personnel - EEOC catalog, 2005 -- 2006; UA042.001.030.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Paid Personnel - Total salary, 2005 -- 2006; UA042.001.030.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Paid Personnel - Pd Faculty Appt., 2005 -- 2006; UA042.001.030.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Paid Personnel - Job cat - M and F, 1995 -- 2006; UA042.001.030.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Paid Personnel - FT / PT, 2000 -- 2006; UA042.001.030.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Summary of degrees granted, 1995 -- 2005; UA042.001.030.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Survey Instruments, 1993; UA042.001.030.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Summer Session Enroll, 1995 -- 2005; UA042.001.030.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Tenure % by department and school, 1995 -- 2006; UA042.001.030.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Web Survey Info, 2001; UA042.001.030.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - July (FY01 Research), 2001; UA042.001.030.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - August (FY01 Research), 2001; UA042.001.030.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - Sept (FY01 Research), 2001; UA042.001.030.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - Oct (FY01 Research), 2001; UA042.001.030.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - Nov (FY01 Research), 2001; UA042.001.030.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - Dec (FY01 Research), 2001; UA042.001.030.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - Jan (FY01 Research), 2000 -- 2003; UA042.001.030.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - Feb (FY01 Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00019a; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - March (FY01 Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00019b; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - April (FY01 Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - May (FY01 Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Office - C141100 - June (FY01 Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Budget Sheets C141100 (FY01 Research con't), 2003; UA042.001.030.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Fact Book (FY01 Research con't), 2000; UA042.001.030.00024; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - IDR's - Misc. (FY01 Research con't), 2000; UA042.001.030.00025; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Supplies (FY01 Research con't), 2000 -- 2001; UA042.001.030.00026; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Printing (FY01 Research con't), 2000 -- 2001; UA042.001.030.00027; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Travel (FY01 Research con't), 2000 -- 2001; UA042.001.030.00028; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 Feb 2001 (FY01 Research con't), UA042.001.030.00029; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - March 2001 Office (FY01 Research con't), UA042.001.030.00030; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 March 2001 (FY01 Research con't), UA042.001.030.00031; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141200 - Cleared - FY 2002 (FY02), UA042.001.030.00032; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141200 - Budget Sheets FY 2002 (FY02), UA042.001.030.00033; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141200 - Cleared (FY02), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00034; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141200 - Budget Sheets (FY02), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00035; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - Budget Sheets FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00036; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - July - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00037; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - August - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00038; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - Sept- FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00039; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - Oct - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00040; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - Nov - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00041; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - Dec - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00042; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - Jan - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00043; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - Feb - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00044; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - Mar - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00045; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - April - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00046; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - May - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), 2000 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00047; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100 - June - FY 2002 (FY02 - Research), UA042.001.030.00048; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - July (FY03 - Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00049; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - August (FY03 - Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00050; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - Sept (FY03 - Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00051; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - October (FY03 - Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00052; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - Nov (FY03 - Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00053; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - Dec (FY03 - Research), 2003; UA042.001.030.00054; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - Jan (FY03 - Research), 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.030.00055; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - Feb (FY03 - Research), 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.030.00056; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - March (FY03 - Research), 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.030.00057; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - April (FY03 - Research), 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.030.00058; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - May (FY03 - Research), 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.030.00059; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Research - C141200 - June (FY03 - Research), 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.030.00060; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - FY03 PC Card Transactions, 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.030.00061; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - PC 2000 (PC Reports), 2000 -- 2001; UA042.001.030.00062; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - C141100- PC Card Reports FY 2002 (PC Reports), 2001 -- 2002; UA042.001.030.00063; Office of Institutional Research (Box 30)
  - Senior Survey (Comments), 1990; UA042.001.031.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - TRENDS - Senior Survey, 1995; UA042.001.031.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [1 of 3], 1997 -- 1999; UA042.001.031.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [2 of 3], 1997 -- 1999; UA042.001.031.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [3 of 3], 1997 -- 1999; UA042.001.031.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [1 of 3], 2000; UA042.001.031.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [2 of 3], 2000; UA042.001.031.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [3 of 3], 2000; UA042.001.031.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey (1) [1 of 3], 2002; UA042.001.031.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey (1) [2 of 3], 2002; UA042.001.031.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey (1) [3 of 3], 2002; UA042.001.031.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey (2) [1 of 2], 2002; UA042.001.031.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey (2) [2 of 2], 2002; UA042.001.031.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [1 of 6], 2001; UA042.001.031.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
    - Senior Survey data merger 2001 (w/ SIS) (SAT scores, GPA, home state, Fin Aid, and majors according to sts), UA042.001.031.00014.00001; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey 2001 / Trends 2, UA042.001.031.00014.00002; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey 2001 / Career Services - Report xcell / Internships - Report xcell / SPSS - GTK, UA042.001.031.00014.00003; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey 2001 - Trends 1 / Historical for campus mail, campus security, classroom, computers, dining, email, laboratory and library, UA042.001.031.00014.00004; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey 2001 / Survey Instrument, UA042.001.031.00014.00005; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey 2001 / Survey Instrument, UA042.001.031.00014.00006; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey NOMS 2001 / Post graduation plans / Major report for Susan Ernst, UA042.001.031.00014.00007; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey 2001 / Alumni Activities Report / Expectations Report / Post graduation Report / Why Why not / Major Report - First Major / Major Report - Second Major, UA042.001.031.00014.00008; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey 2001 / Sr Survey 2001 - SIS / Major Advisors II / Jobs by salary / Jobs by major / Jobs by field / Intended by actual major / Honorary final, UA042.001.031.00014.00009; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey 2001 / Comments - Final, UA042.001.031.00014.00010; Office of Institutional Research
  - Senior Survey [2 of 6], 2001; UA042.001.031.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [3 of 6], 2001; UA042.001.031.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [4 of 6], 2001; UA042.001.031.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [5 of 6], 2001; UA042.001.031.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [6 of 6], 2001; UA042.001.031.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 31)
  - Senior Survey [1 of 6], 2002; UA042.001.032.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
    - Senior Survey 2002, UA042.001.032.00001.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Senior Survey [2 of 6], 2002; UA042.001.032.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - Senior Survey [3 of 6], 2002; UA042.001.032.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - Senior Survey [4 of 6], 2002; UA042.001.032.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - Senior Survey [5 of 6], 2002; UA042.001.032.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - Senior Survey [6 of 6], 2002; UA042.001.032.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS [1 of 3], 1999; UA042.001.032.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS [2 of 3], 1999; UA042.001.032.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS [3 of 3], 1999; UA042.001.032.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS [1 of 3], 2000; UA042.001.032.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS [2 of 3], 2000; UA042.001.032.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS [3 of 3], 2000; UA042.001.032.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS, 2001; UA042.001.032.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS 2002-2003 [1 of 4], 2001 -- 2003; UA042.001.032.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
    - HEDS Consortium / Prepared for: Tufts / HEDS Freshman Financial Aid, Fall, 2001-10-02; UA042.001.032.00014.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - HEDS [2 of 4], 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.032.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS [3 of 4], 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.032.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS [4 of 4], 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.032.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 32)
  - HEDS [Correspondence], 2004; UA042.001.033.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS [Binder] [1 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.033.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS [Binder] [2 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.033.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS [Binder] [3 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.033.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS [Correspondence], 2005; UA042.001.033.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS [Binder], 2005; UA042.001.033.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Book 1 [1 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.033.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Book 1 [2 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.033.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Book 1 [3 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.033.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Book 2 [1 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.033.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Book 2 [2 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.033.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Book 2 [3 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.033.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1974; UA042.001.033.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1975; UA042.001.033.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1976; UA042.001.033.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1977; UA042.001.033.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1978; UA042.001.033.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1979; UA042.001.033.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1979 -- 1980; UA042.001.033.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1980 -- 1981; UA042.001.033.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1981 -- 1982; UA042.001.033.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions - IPEDS, 1987 -- 1988; UA042.001.033.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions - IPEDS, 1988 -- 1989; UA042.001.033.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1989 -- 1990; UA042.001.033.00024; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1990 -- 1991; UA042.001.033.00025; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.033.00026; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.033.00027; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.033.00028; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.033.00029; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.033.00030; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.033.00031; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - Completions - IPEDS, 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.033.00032; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Volume 2 [1 of 3], 1992; UA042.001.033.00033; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Volume 2 [2 of 3], 1992; UA042.001.033.00034; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Volume 2 [3 of 3], 1992; UA042.001.033.00035; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [1 of 4], 1992; UA042.001.033.00036; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [2 of 4], 1992; UA042.001.033.00037; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [3 of 4], 1992; UA042.001.033.00038; Office of Institutional Research (Box 33)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [1 of 2], 1993; UA042.001.034.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [2 of 2], 1993; UA042.001.034.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - HEDS Reports Series Book 1 of 2 [1 of 4], 1997; UA042.001.034.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - HEDS Reports Series Book 1 of 2 [2 of 4], 1997; UA042.001.034.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - HEDS Reports Series Book 1 of 2 [3 of 4], 1997; UA042.001.034.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - HEDS Reports Series Book 1 of 2 [4 of 4], 1997; UA042.001.034.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - HEDS Reports Series Book 2 of 2 [1 of 3], 1997; UA042.001.034.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - HEDS Reports Series Book 2 of 2 [2 of 3], 1997; UA042.001.034.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - HEDS Reports Series Book 2 of 2 [3 of 3], 1997; UA042.001.034.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued [1 of 4], 1987; UA042.001.034.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued [2 of 4], 1987; UA042.001.034.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued [3 of 4], 1987; UA042.001.034.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued [4 of 4], 1987; UA042.001.034.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued B [1 of 4], 1988; UA042.001.034.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued B [2 of 4], 1988; UA042.001.034.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued B [3 of 4], 1988; UA042.001.034.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued B [4 of 4], 1988; UA042.001.034.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued [1 of 3], 1990; UA042.001.034.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued [2 of 3], 1990; UA042.001.034.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - Reports Issued [3 of 3], 1990; UA042.001.034.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 34)
  - HEDS Vol. 1 [1 of 3], 1991; UA042.001.035.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Vol. 1 [2 of 3], 1991; UA042.001.035.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Vol. 1 [3 of 3], 1991; UA042.001.035.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Vol. 2 [1 of 4], 1991; UA042.001.035.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Vol. 2 [2 of 4], 1991; UA042.001.035.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Vol. 2 [3 of 4], 1991; UA042.001.035.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Vol. 2 [4 of 4], 1991; UA042.001.035.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 1 of 2 [1 of 3], 1995; UA042.001.035.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 1 of 2 [2 of 3], 1995; UA042.001.035.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 1 of 2 [3 of 3], 1995; UA042.001.035.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 1 of 2 [1 of 3], 1996; UA042.001.035.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 1 of 2 [2 of 3], 1996; UA042.001.035.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 1 of 2 [3 of 3], 1996; UA042.001.035.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 2 of 2 [1 of 3], 1996; UA042.001.035.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 2 of 2 [2 of 3], 1996; UA042.001.035.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 2 of 2 [3 of 3], 1996; UA042.001.035.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 2 of 2 [1 of 3], 1995; UA042.001.035.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 2 of 2 [2 of 3], 1995; UA042.001.035.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Report Series Book 2 of 2 [3 of 3], 1995; UA042.001.035.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Alumni/ae Survey Project, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.035.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HED and COFHE Agreement (HEDS), 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.035.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Data Rec'd, 1990 -- 1991; UA042.001.035.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Data (Responses), 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.035.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 35)
  - HEDS Data [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.036.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - HEDS Data [2 of 2], 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.036.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - HEDS Data Sharing Requests and Received Data [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1990; UA042.001.036.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - HEDS Data Sharing Requests and Received Data [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1990; UA042.001.036.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - HEDS Degrees Granted Report, 1987; UA042.001.036.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - HEDS Requests, 1990 -- 1991; UA042.001.036.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - HEDS University Salary Data Exchange (Faculty Salaries) 97-98 87-88, 1987 -- 1998; UA042.001.036.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)